(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T16:30:32.936753",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
Unbeatable smile, stirring up the media
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
I want to know that secret, mysterious
抜け出してるさえ彼女のエリア
Even slipping away is her territory
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You, so perfect and full of lies,
天才的なアイドル様
Are a genius idol-sama!
You're my savior, you're my saving grace
今日何食べた？ 好きな本は？
What did you eat today? What book do you love?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
Whenever you go out to play, where do you go?
何も食べてない それは内緒
Haven't eaten anything, that's a secret
何を聞かれてものらりくらり
Answering evasively to any question
そう淡々と けれど燦々と
So nonchalantly, yet brilliantly glowing
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
A seemingly unseen secret is the taste of honey
あれもないないない これもないないない
There's none of that, none of this either
好きなタイプは？ 相手は？ さあ答えて
What's your type? Who's your partner? Come on, answer
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からないからさ」
"I don't even know what it's like to love someone"
嘘か本当か知り得ないそんな言葉にまた一人生誕する
Yet another person is born from words where truth and lies blend
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone gets their eyes stolen away
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
You are the perfect and ultimate idol
金輪際現れない 一番星の生まれ変わり
Unrivaled, never to appear again, the reincarnation of the brightest star
その笑顔で愛してるで 誰ても彼ても虜にしていく
With that smile saying 'I love you', making everyone her captive
その瞳が その言葉が 嘘でもそれは完璧なアイ
Even if those eyes and words are lies, it's perfect love
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yes, yes, that girl is special
我々はモブのその他大勢です お星様の引き立て役Bです
We are just extras in the crowd, supporting role B
全てがあの子のお陰なわけない 痺れるような嫉妬なんてないわけがない
It can't be all thanks to her, of course there's paralyzing jealousy
これはネタじゃないからこそ許せない 完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない
This isn't a joke, which is why I can't forgive it, can't forgive an imperfect you
自分を許せない 誰より強い君以外は認めない
Can't forgive myself, I won't accept anyone other than you, stronger than anyone
誰もが信じ崇めてる まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Everyone worships and believes in you, truly the strongest and invincible idol
弱点なんて見当たらない 一番星を宿している
No weaknesses to be found, harboring the brightest star
ここはカンパニーじゃない隠し味ない
This isn't a company, no hidden flavors
然るべき言葉にまさか一人倒る
Struck down by the words that must be said
誰もがしがみつく誰も彼も奪われていく
Everyone clings on, everyone gets taken away
君は完璧で究極のアイドル 金輪際現れない
You are the perfect, ultimate idol, never to appear again
秘密はそう言われなくていい それこそ本物の愛
Secrets don't need to be told, that is true love
得意の笑顔でおかすメディア 隠し切るこの秘密だけは
Media tainted by that signature smile, hiding away this sole secret
愛してるって嘘で積むキャリア これこそやり抜くための唯一の道だ
Building a career piled on the lie of 'I love you', this is the only way to carry it through
いつか報われるかななんてね 言ってた
Wondering if it'll ever pay off, so she said
嘘か本当か分からないそんなことばかり
Filled with things where you never know what's true or false
本当のことさえ口に出せない そんなんじゃいられない
Can't even speak the truth, can't stay like that
どんな言葉も君を強くする 完全じゃない君じゃ許せない
Every word makes you stronger, can't forgive an imperfect you
自分を許せない 誰より強い君以外は認めない
Can't forgive myself, won't accept anyone other than you, stronger than anyone
誰もが信じ崇めてる まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Everyone worships and believes in you, truly the strongest and invincible idol
弱点なんて見当たらない 一番星を宿している
No weaknesses to be found, harboring the brightest star
小さしがみつく誰も彼も愛したいわけじゃない
Not that she wants to love everyone clinging to her
誰もが手を引く 流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
Everyone reaches out, even the flowing sweat is a beautiful aqua
ルブ眼の裏に光るルビー 踊るように舞うその姿に
A ruby shining behind the blue eyes, dancing and twirling in that form
誰もが魅せられていく
Everyone is left completely captivated.
いたずらな天気雨みたい
It's like a mischievous sun shower,
曖昧ではっきりしない夜
An ambiguous and unclear night.
ささくれて消えることのない
Never to fray and disappear,
ほころんだ夢爛々光る
A frayed dream shines vividly.
「愛してる」
"I love you"—
そんな言葉じゃ足りない
Such words are not enough.
誰かに愛されたことも
Being loved by someone,
誰かのこと愛したこともない
Or loving someone else—never happened.
そんな私の嘘がいつか本当になること信じてる
I believe that lie of mine will someday become true.
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
Someday I'll surely get everything in my hands.
私はそういう気まぐれなアイドル
I'm that kind of fickle idol.
と信じないでみんなのこと
Don't believe me when I say I love everyone—
ちゃんと愛したいから今日も
Because I truly want to love you today too.
不器用なこの言葉が本当になるように願って
I wish for these clumsy words to become real.
それでもまだ君と君にだけは言えずにいたけど
Even so, to you and only you, I couldn't say it.
ああやっと言えた これは絶対嘘じゃない愛してる
Ah, I finally said it. This is no lie—I love you.
Hey, Kronii is here!
Whew, I hope that was good.
And well, I hope I look like an idol on stage.
And if you like the performance so far, be sure to use the hashtag #3DRonii.
And if you like the show, use the hashtag #3DRonii.
And, well, speaking of the stage, take a look at this!
It's so beautiful, and it's like the stage was like made for me, and only me.
It's so beautiful, like it was made for me and only me.
Look, look at just how grand it is.
Look, just look at how grand it is.
And, well, it's looking a little too bright right now, so shall we turn it down a bit?
It's a little too bright, so shall we turn it down?
Whew. Okay, that is much better.
Oh, yeah, I guess I forgot to tell you, this can change from daytime to nighttime. I can control the time of day according to my will.
I can change it from day to night according to my will.
Oh, wait! Hey! Wait, wait, wait, look at you. Wait, you got invited? What?
Oh, wait! Hey, wait, look at you. You got invited? What?
How many supers did you have to pay to get that VIP seat?
How many supers did you pay for that VIP seat?
What? Wait, and you? What? Get out of here, I didn't invite you.
What? And you? Get out of here, I didn't invite you.
Oh, yeah, uh, how'd you think about the song?
Um, I know it's pretty overdone, but I thought it was pretty fitting for this show today, don't you think?
It's overdone, but fitting for today, don't you think?
But, yeah, it's a pretty good start for today, but it doesn't stop there.
It's a good start, but it doesn't stop there.
Because stay tuned, the first-ever Kronii Awards is happening right now, today, tonight, with all of you and all of me.
Stay tuned for the first-ever Kronii Awards tonight!
Was that mean?
Well, you got to stick around for that.
All right, let's get this show on the road. Take a look at this.
All right, let's get this show on the road.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Kronii Awards.
Today we'll be joined by not one, not two, not even three, but four different Kronies!
Today we'll be joined by four different Kronies!
That's right! And each Kronii will display their amazing talents, and the best one will receive the award in this...
Each Kronii will display their amazing talents!
Yeah,
uh let me show you what
this sick award is going to look like. Give me a second.
All right, here it is!
That's right, it's the golden Kronii trophy.
I know, it's looking pretty amazing.
I want it in my room, I want it plastered everywhere.
Man, whoever gets this will be a lucky Kronii, gold and...
But you know, that's whatever.
None of my concern cuz I'm not participating, unfortunately.
With that, let me introduce today's participants.
First off, we have, you guessed it, miss Oro Kronii!
Let's all give a warm welcome to Kronii
with the actress role! Woohoo! Onwards!
Fall down to your queen, it's your majesty.
And, well, I believe I should win because, I mean, just look at me.
If I don't, I believe it's heresy.
And everyone who didn't vote for me
should be sentenced for life because that's what they deserve.
And, well, anyway, I don't know if you can already tell,
but I'll be reenacting Snow White today.
And, you know, you can obviously tell with the crown and the apple,
but I'll be the queen.
That's going to be exciting. I know, I fit the role so well, so we'll see.
And with that, shall we begin? Feast your eyes!
Hmm, okay, let's see here.
I don't know if this mirror is actually going to work, so, hmm.
I think I might give it a little bit of a test run.
Yes! What an amazing idea, Kronii. Thank you.
Okay, well, ahem.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall, who is the cutest of them all?
Boros? Uh, I mean,
Dread Boros is pretty cute, I guess. Um,
Yeah, it's a cute little snake boy, okay?
Yeah, it works. It works. Okay, you can you can go now, okay? Thank you.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall, who is the fairest of them all?
What? Are you serious? Is this broken?
No, don't give me that happy face. Get out of here!
Disgusting! My God! Okay, uh whatever.
I got to get that image out of the way.
Maybe they don't understand what fairest means. Okay.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall, who is the most beautiful of them all?
Okay, that was weird. Um, I...
I don't
Mm. Okay.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
And you best be right this time, or else I'm going to hand you over to a second-hand shop. It's your last chance.
Who is the fairest of them all?
Hey!
Oh my god, what took you so long?
Oh, you know, I was just doing my hair.
Oh, please. You look better with or without. You're always so on point, girl.
Oh, you, you're always so humble.
Oh, stop it. So, like, what's up?
Uh, excuse me? Didn't you hear? I was like calling you multiple times. Oh, well, I hadn't call you, but you know, when people say who's the prettiest girl in town, I mean, you know, I mean...
Uh, excuse me? Didn't you hear? I was like calling you multiple times. Oh, well, I hadn't called you, but you know, when people say who's the prettiest girl in town, I mean, you know, I mean...
prettiest girl in town, look around, it has to be you.
Well, yeah, but...
Hey!
I guess...
I guess you don't look half bad yourself. I think you could probably take second place even, or even first place.
Hey!
So, what are you doing after this?
Uh, you know, just hanging out, relaxing, alone, completely free. Nothing going on.
Um, up for some 1v1 or some local multiplayer?
Oh...
Was that an invitation?
Take it as you will.
You know what? I think I will.
Hey!
We're going to save that for later.
Yeah, keep it on the lowdown and get out of here.
No, you get out of here.
No, you stop it.
I'm going to chuck this apple at you if you don't go.
Oh, you know what? I'm going to get out of your hair. I'm just going to...
No, no, no, I'm going to get out first.
No, no, it's fine, I'll go first.
No, it's fine, it's fine, stop it. I'll be the bigger person here.
What? I'm the bigger person here.
Yeah? Well, watch me leave.
Oh my god. No, stop. Oh my gosh.
Can't believe she did that. Oh my gosh. That silly girl. Goodness.
Oh, yeah, yeah. We were on screen, right?
Um, well, thank you so much. I I hope you liked our little performance.
It was pretty great. I mean, my performance, but our our could also work.
And well, an apple a day keeps the doctor away.
Yeah. Why did I say that?
I don't really know, but that is the moral of the story.
Yes. Apples, apples are very good for you.
Okay, well, anyway, I got things to take care of, so toodaloo and bye-bye.
Thank you so much for that wonderful act, Miss Kronii. Your performance was truly moving,
and I could sense the chemistry between Mirror Kronii and Kronii, and
truly, I would love to see that show again, if I could.
And you know what? I think I like it so much that I'll watch the vod again later.
I mean, what?
Anyway,
next up, let's call the next Kronii up to the stage.
Let's all give her a warm round of applause.
Let's go! She needs it.
She doesn't really, she's got the confidence, but let's just give her an applause.
Woohoo!
Um, hi!
Um, yeah, uh it'd be nice if I can win, because I, you know, worked hard.
Yeah, oh, um by the way, I'm uh Singronii. I'm the one that sings, if you can't tell from the the idol outfit and everything.
Yeah, oh, um by the way, I'm uh Singronii. I'm the one that sings, if you can't tell from the idol outfit and everything.
Um, kind of camera shy.
I don't really know what to do in this kind of situation. Um, but yeah,
I'm gonna try my best, so it'd be nice if you guys like it too.
Um, but but if you don't, it's it's it's okay. That that's okay, too.
Ah, okay. Please uh listen to this song, Charles.
さよならはあなたから言った
You said goodbye to me first,
それなのに頬を濡らしてしまうの
and yet here I am wetting my cheeks.
そうやって昨日の事も消してしまうなら
If you're gonna make yesterday go away like that,
もういいよ 笑って
I'm done, just smile.
花束を抱えて歩いた
I walked with a bouquet of flowers,
意味もなくただ街を下ろした
for no reason at all, looking down on the city.
こうやって理想の縁に心を置き去っていくの
I'm leaving my heart on the edge of an ideal.
もういいか 空っぽでいいや
I'll stay empty, let's keep it empty.
それでいつか深い青で満たしたのなら
And one day, if I fill it with deep blue...
どうだろう こんな風に悩むのかな
I wonder if I can be troubled like this.
愛を 囁いて 囁いて 雲の上
Singing 'bout our love, our love from high above,
濁りきっては見えないや
but through the clouds I cannot see enough, oh no.
いや いや
No, no!
遠く描いていた日々を
The days we pictured far away...
語って 語って 夜の群れ
we talk and talk about in the dusk of night,
いがみ合って きりがないな
bickering on without an end.
いや いや いや
No, no, no!
笑い合って さよなら
Until we laugh it off and say goodbye.
朝焼けと あなたの溜息
Morning comes along, the familiar sound of your sigh.
この街は 僕等の夢を見ている
This town we live in is watching over our dreams.
今日だって 互いの事を
Today as well, we're going to forget
忘れていくんだね
'bout each other bit by bit.
ねえ そうでしょう
Isn't that right?
黙って いよう それでいつか
It's time to stop our words though some days it could hurt...
芽生えたとしても別に良いんだよ
but it will be okay because this sorrow may have meaning.
こんな愁いも意味があるなら
If there's meaning to this sorrow.
恋と飾って 飾って 静かな方へ
Hiding 'hind our love, our love as if we made up,
汚れきった言葉を 今 今 今
but still the filthy thoughts are slipping out now, now, now!
「此処には誰もいない」
"There's no one here."
「ええ そうだね」
"Yes, you're right."
混ざって 混ざって 二人の果て
We mix and blend, and in the end of us...
譲り合って 何もないな
We give and take, but there's nothing to it.
いや いや いや
No, no, no!
痛みだって教えて きっときっとわかっていた
Tell me what pain is, surely, surely we knew...
騙し合うなんて馬鹿らしいよな
How absurd it is to fool each other.
ずっとずっと迷っていた ほらね僕等は変われない
Always, always lost we are, see, we always are the same.
そうだろう 互いのせいであって
That's right, now we're here thanks to each other,
今があるのにな
even though we have the present.
愛を 囁いて 囁いて 雲の上
Singing 'bout our love, our love from high above,
濁りきっては見えないや
but through the clouds I cannot see enough, oh no.
いや いや いや
No, no, no!
日々に増えていた後悔を
The regret that keeps piling up day by day,
語って 語って 夜の群れ
which we talk and talk about in the dusk of night.
許し合って意味もないな
Even if we forgive each other, there's no meaning to it.
いや いや いや
No, no, no!
さよならはあなたから言った
You said goodbye to me first
花束を抱えて歩いた
I walked carrying a bouquet of flowers
さようなら
Goodbye
はあ、オッケー。
Hah... Okay.
みんな気に入ってくれたらいいな。
Um, I hope you guys like that.
ふう、けっこう疲れたけど、
Ugh, that was pretty tiring, but
うん、ベストを尽くしたと思う。
yeah, I'd like to think I did my best,
だから、もしかしたら受賞できるかも……？　わからないけど。
so hopefully I can... maybe be considered to win? I don't know.
お、みんなポーズが見たいの？　……かな？
Oh, do you guys want to see some poses? I guess?
オッケー、変なお願いだけど、やってみる。
Okay. Odd request, but I'll try.
ええっと、うん、輝いてる？
Uh... yeah. Glowing.
だから、ええと、どんなポーズがほしい？　こんな感じ？　ちょっとこんな感じ？　よくわからないけど。
So let's see, what kind of pose do you want? Like like this? Like maybe a little bit like that? I don't really know.
ええと、こんな感じ？　みんなが何がいいのかあまりよくわからないけど。
Um, like maybe like this? I'm not really sure what you guys want.
こんな感じ？　ハッピー？　これっていいのかな？
Like that? Happy? Is- is this good?
もうひとつ、最後の一つ……。
One- one last one...
もうやったよ、もうやった。
I already... I already did one.
うん、これでおしまい。これで全部。
Yeah, that's it. That's all for me.
もう行くね。オッケー、行くよ。
I'm going to... I'm going to go now. Okay.
このカメラを顔からどけて。じゃあね！
Get this camera out of my face. Okay, bye!
ミス・クロニー、素晴らしい歌をありがとうございました！
Thank you very much, Miss Kronii, for that amazing song!
あなたの歌声は私たちのハートをしっかり捉えました。私のハートもね、実はいちばん大事なやつ。
Your singing definitely has captured our hearts. My heart, in fact, which is the most important one.
そして次は、次のクロニーをステージに呼びましょう！　みんなで温かい拍手を送りましょう！
And next up, we're going to call the next Kronii up on stage and let's all give her a warm round of applause!
あ、でも、ショーを続ける前に、ちょっとコマーシャルを挟みます！
Oh, but before we get on with the show, we're going to have a bit of a commercial break!
そう、私たちはスポンサーに……誰か当ててみて。
That's right, we are sponsored by... guess who it is?
そう、正解！　ミス・オロ・クロニー！　なんて素敵なギャルなんだ！
Yep, you got it! Miss Ouro Kronii! Oh my goodness, what a given gal!
ありがとう、ありがとう本当にクロニー！　どういたしまして。え？
Thank you, thank you so much, Kronii! You're welcome! What?
とにかく、ショーを続けよう！　コマーシャルブレイクと共に！　ウッホー！
Anyway, let's get on with the show! With the commercial break! Woohoo!
ええ、何が起きたの？　私は勝ちに来たの！
Hey, what is up! I'm here to win!
そしてなぜかって？　それは私がすごく的確だからよ。分かった？　だって、ほら、剣だから。
And you know why? It's because I'm so on point. Get it? 'Cause you know, swords...
私は今日とてもシャープでウィットに富んでいる。はは！　またやっちゃった。
I'm so sharp and witty today. Haha! I did it again.
ああもう、私って本当にバカみたい。信じられないくらい。これ以上どうやったら良くなれるの？
Oh man, I'm so silly like that. It's mind-blowing. How could I get any better than this?
ええと、今日はフルーツを切って、フルーツサラダを作ります！
Well, today I'm going to be chopping up some fruit and make some fruit salad!
Oh.
This is going to be a great. It's going to be a fun time.
This is going to be great. It's going to be a fun time.
Oh!
Oh, thank you, Kronii.
What's that?
Pineapple? That's so cute! Thank you.
Yeah, I'm going to be chopping these up for today. So, that's going to be exciting.
Thank you so much for showing it off.
And with that, Kronies, standby.
And with that, Kronies, stand by.
All right. Good, good, good. Back in position.
It's time to show you all what I got. Music start! Let's go!
Fruits. Come on, let's go.
Sick, sick, sick.
Damn, look at that.
I'm doing so good. Look at that accuracy. Insane.
I'm doing so good. Look at the accuracy. Insane.
Bam! Boom! Bring 'em. Ugh.
Look at that. One shot. One kill. Amazing.
Oh, oh, time stop! Ugh, okay.
Uh, okay, this one's pretty durable. Oh, look at that. Okay, nice, nice.
You guys didn't see anything. Perfect.
Just one cut. One clean cut.
Oh, man. That was great and all, but you know.
I'm kind of not feeling it. I wish I could spice things up.
But I don't know how.
Well, what what what can I do? Can I do?
Oh.
What? What?
Guys, you want to join, too?
No, I'm making fruit salad, not clock salad. What the heck?
Okay. Well, you asked for it.
Ah, the things I do. All right, come on up.
Ugh.
Yeah.
You're so durable. What the heck? You're so thick. Lose some weight, bro.
Man, what a what a hassle.
I'm I'm like surrounded by Kronies with some weird weird things that I can't really say on the show.
But anyway, I got to patch you guys up now.
Okay. See, good as good as new.
Yay.
You're welcome, guys. Always have to make things weird for me, but you know what? I'll live with it.
Anyway, I got the stage just a little bit dirty with all the fruit juice, um oil maybe.
I don't even know. But I hope you all enjoyed it.
And with that, I'm going to go. Kronii, out.
Woo! Yeah! Come on!
Thank you for that stunning display, Miss Kronii.
Um the the stage is a bit soiled with all the fruit juice, but um let's not mind that.
Because the next Kronii will help with the mess.
Ooh, what'd that mean? Oh my goodness! Who could the next Kronii be?
But let's not keep the suspense any longer.
Next up, the next Kronii is coming up on stage. Let's all give her a warm round of applause.
Woo!
Yo, what's up? It's me, Washeronii.
You know, it's uh good to be here. Um I think the reason why I should win is because I'm so chill, everyone's angry or just so hyper and I'm just like down with the chillness, you know?
And also, I'm here to make this world a cleaner place with my awesome power washer here. So, yeah. Let's
Wash up, MyDoonies!
Haha, get it?
It's like a pun on What's Up,
on what's up, but I'm washing things so it's wash up.
but I'm washing things, so it's Wash Up.
I'm funny too. Damn.
Funny Kronii, watch out.
Okay, laying it away.
Let's get this job done and over with. Let's do this. Woohoo.
All right, I'm here to wash.
Let's do this. Ooh.
Oh man, this statue is looking so gnarly, bro. Woo.
All right, okay. Well, let's begin.
Damn, this is like so dirty.
Dude, is it from the fruit juice? Like what happened in this place?
Like, man, that's insane.
And like, the statue's so big and just so small.
This world is just so big,
and I'm like a speck of dust, or what am I?
I think about life, really.
Oh, okay, looks done.
Damn, time passes so fast when I'm just cleaning.
Damn, but yeah, that looks great.
Oh, what? There's another one?
Okay, well, actually, I'm not complaining.
More cleaning for me. Woohoo.
Let's go. Yeah.
Dude, this is so therapeutic.
Like, I can do this all day, man.
You know, Kronii's legs are so long,
like, what does she do?
Just so beautiful, and her being in gold just makes it so much better, you know?
That's like the best part.
Look at that.
Oh, gold Kronii in all her glory.
It's, it's done.
It's done, it's my masterpiece.
Woo.
Well, it seems like my work here is done,
with all this beautiful statues restored to its former glory.
Man, if you need any help, you can call me anytime.
I'm just going to wash everything, like, shh.
Shh, shh.
That's going to be donezo because I'm just so amazing like that.
Rock on, bro.
And you know, I hope that as quick as it was because of my pro skills,
I hope everybody enjoyed this therapy session,
because it always is therapeutic for me.
So yeah, with that,
I'm going to bid you adieu.
MyDoonies, see you around.
Or not.
All right, bye bye.
Shh, shh, shh. Yeah.
Ooh, look at that!
Wow, this stage is now squeaky clean.
Look at that!
I can almost see the reflection of myself.
Oh my goodness, your ears are beautiful.
Uh, okay, anyway, thank you so much to PowerWash Kronii,
and that is all the performances we have for today.
I know, I know.
All right, oh well.
But thank you to our fellow participants for showing off your beautiful, stunning abilities.
No wonder there were four Kroniis, because uh, if we were to show off one Kronii, then this would have taken forever.
How could we just, you04:47.335 know, narrow it down to just one hour?
How could we just, you know, narrow it down to just one hour?
It's going to be like six hours or 48 hours or god knows how long. But, yeah.
it's uh lucky for you guys or unlucky?
I don't know. But anyway, let's move on to the award ceremony.
Woohoo! Let's go!
And there we have it, those were
all the performances we had for tonight.
What an amazing turnout, as expected from me, obviously.
Uh, now, now, if our fabulous guests are lucky, they might have the chance of grabbing this absolutely
Now, if our fabulous guests are lucky, they might have the chance of grabbing this absolutely
glorious Kronii statue, endorsed by again, me, Kronii.
And oh, it's so shiny. Gosh, I wish I could get one.
But I'm not participating, so... sigh. Oh well.
But I'm not participating, so... Oh well.
But with that,
let's hear from the nominees, their thoughts on their stunning performances tonight.
To start us off, let's hear from Qronii!
I felt a little bit heated towards the end,
but I really do feel like I conveyed the feelings of Kronii very much so.
At being at all, I truly believe all Kroniis are beautiful in their own respective ways.
At any rate, I truly believe all Kroniis are beautiful in their own respective ways.
These amazing qualities of mine: understanding, humble, and most of all, attractive.
Oh, what defines me as the supreme overlord?
What defines me as the supreme overlord?
Everyone loves me,
because who wouldn't?
They should all bow before my raw awesomeness.
And because of that and only for that reason, I deserve the award. A slayer!
Thank you, Qronii.
How humble of you.
Wow, um, I think, but I love the apple by the way. Can I, can I touch it?
Ooh! Oh my gosh!
That's that is amazing. That is fresh. Damn.
That is amazing. That is fresh. Damn.
Oh, oh okay. I'm too mesmerized.
Oh, okay. I'm too mesmerized.
Anyway, up next is Singronii. Let's hear it!
I feel like I tried to do my best.
Um I hope it shows and um you know, I guess for that effort,
I hope it shows and, um, you know, I guess for that effort,
it would be an honor to receive the award, but uh if not, that that's okay.
it would be an honor to receive the award, but if not, that's okay.
Um I guess I'll just try harder next time. Um I mean I've been practicing,
I guess I'll just try harder next time. I mean, I've been practicing,
uh so you know, maybe next time I'll do much better and um win, I guess I just got to do better.
so, you know, maybe next time I'll do much better and win. I guess I just got to do better.
Just just do better, right? Yeah. Yeah.
Just do better, right? Yeah.
No um anyway, I should just pass it on to the next person.
Anyway, I should just pass it on to the next person.
Singronii, we wish you luck on your idol journey.
And I see what you did there with the idol outfit. Clever, very clever. Cute too.
Okay, she looks like she's about to cry, so let's just move on right here, okay?
Funnyronii, let's hear what kind of words you have to say about today's performance.
If you don't think that I deserve it,
then I think you need to have better taste in humor,
because you lack common sense and any reason an average human is supposed to have.
And besides, did you see the Croniis? They seemed to have liked it.
Like, I mean, they were literally jumping at the opportunity to be part of the performance.
And sure, they ended up in the hospital and are suffering and all that fun stuff.
But that's entertainment for you, you know?
No pain, no gain.
And there was a lot of gain to be had.
What exactly is it?
I'm not going to tell you that.
You've got to find the answer yourself, buddy.
You gotta find the answer yourself, buddy.
Since you're the funny one here,
I'll go ahead and assume you're joking there.
But if you don't win this time, you're definitely in the running for
most humble next to Dronii over there.
Okay, last but not least,
let's hear it from Cleaneronii!
Uh, like,
it was always such a radical experience, dude.
And I felt like my soul was being cleansed
along with the dirt,
like, totally tubular, man.
What was like, going off on those statues, like,
watch out, watch out, you know?
Like, dude, there was like a swell time,
I was like, frothing at the mouth almost,
'cause like, dude, I was like the Mother Pearl kind of experience, you know?
Yeah. Yeah, you get it. Yeah.
And there we have it.
Um, thank you for all your rather interesting speeches.
I'm sure someone out there, far, far out there will find them heartwarming. Maybe.
You know what? Since I'm here, I think I'll make a little speech too.
You know, why not? After all, I did my hair extra special for today and everything.
So, I deserve it because I was the main organizer, first of all,
and also, I'm the only Kronii here with a clock.
Yes, I made it extra large for today, and I came prepared.
And I honestly look the best out of everyone here.
No offense. I'm not saying that I'm part of the candidates,
but if I was, I would be the MVP here. You know, that's-- that's all from me though.
Oh, you guys, stop it. You don't have to give me those charming looks.
I know I'm pretty, amazing, cool, talented, absolutely just out of this world and...
Oh, oh, um, it looks like we're finally ready to announce the winner.
Let's see, the votes are in, the polls are shut, and without further ado, the Kroniis have decided.
The winner of this time's glorious Kronii Awards Award Show is...
See, who could it be? Who-- who could it be? It's me!
Ah, yes. My baby is finally here back home in my arms.
Thank you so much for this award, and I'd like to thank everybody who made this possible.
Not you guys, me, myself, and I.
Of course I have to win! Who's the one that planned all this, huh? Look around, say wah!
So?
Sorry, I can't hear, because it seems like your mics have suddenly stopped working.
Oh, what a shame.
And oh, oh look at that, the show's ending! Oh, oh no! Oh no!
Thank you to everyone who tuned in, and stay safe out there, and remember,
maybe next time you too could be right here, standing where I'm standing.
One day, maybe.
Ha, who am I kidding?
Bye!
So, how was it?
Aren't they just amazing?
Thank you so much for watching up to this point.
And now, a few announcements here. What do you think it's gonna be? Let's see.
Bam!
It's a blanket! And not just any blanket, it's inspired by my cape,
that's right. Look at this.
But, you'll have to wait a little bit longer. I know you want this cape ASAP,
but you can get it after the 3D group collab, so keep an eye out for that, okay?
Yay!
And now, you can join my club, Cape Gang! Woohoo!
So, what are you waiting for? Go get it right now! Don't you want this cape?
It's going to be available as soon as the showcase ends, so keep an eye out for that, okay?
Um, but before we end things, I have a short message for everyone.
Yeah, I know, ooh, sudden unplanned stuff, oh my.
Okay, well, you guys want to see a magic trick?
I don't have anything in my hands right now,
but now I do! Whoa, magic!
All right. Let's see. Um...
So, I never would have expected to ever be here years before all this,
and because of you guys, I'm able to have this chance to experience so many new things and meet so many people in just one lifetime.
So, thank you for helping me break out of my shell, and I hope we can continue accomplishing great things together.
Uh, yeah. Yeah. Well, uh, time to get the sappy stuff out of the way. Um,
Okay, but before we end things off, let's uh finish it off with a song. Let's go.
And the final song is going to be for one of my favorite anime, and it's going to be called Eternal Snow, so please give it a listen. Thank you.
君を好きになって どれくらい経つのかな？
How long has it been since I fell in love with you?
気持ち膨らんでゆくばかりで
My feelings just keep growing and growing,
君はこの思い気付いているのかな 一度も言葉にはしてないけど
I wonder if you've noticed these feelings, even though I've never put them into words.
雪のようにただ静かに 降り積もり続けてゆく
Like snow, they just fall and quietly pile up.
君を好きになって どれくらい経つのかナ
How long has it been since I fell in love with you?
気持ちふらりんて ゆくばかりで
My feelings just keep drifting away.
君はこの思い 気づいているのかナ
Will you notice these feelings of mine?
一度も言葉には してないけれど
Even though I've never once put them into words,
雪のように ただ静かに 降り積もりつづけてゆく
Like snow, they just quietly keep accumulating.
hold me tight こんな思いなら
Hold me tight - if this is how it feels,
誰かを 好きになる気持ち
I didn't want to know what it was like
知りたくなかったよ
to be in love with someone.
i love you 涙 止まらない
I love you - my tears won't stop,
こんなんじゃ 君のこと
And so I wish that I had never met you.
知らずに いれば 良かったよ
That I had never known you.
君を いつまで 思っているのかナ
How long will I be thinking of you?
ため息が 窓ガラス 曇らせた
My sighs fogged up the window glass.
揺れる心 灯す キャンドルで
Can a candle flame still melt my trembling heart?
hold me tight 折れるほど強く
Hold me tight, tight enough to break me,
木枯らし 吹雪に出会っても 寒くないように と
So that even in a bitter wind or blizzard, I won't feel cold.
i miss you 君を 思うたび
I miss you - every time I think of you,
編みかけの このマフラー
This half-finished muffler,
今夜も 一人 抱きしめるよ
Tonight, too, I hold it all alone.
永遠に 降る雪があるなら
If there was an eternally falling snow,
君へと 続く この思い 隠せるのかナ
Could it hide my feelings for you?
hold me tight こんな思いなら
Hold me tight - if this is how it feels,
誰かを 好きになる気持ち
I didn't want to know what it was like
知りたくなかったよ
to be in love with someone.
i love you 胸に 込み上げる
I love you - the feeling wells up in my chest,
冬空に 叫ぶ たい
I want to shout to the wintery sky,
今 すぐ 君に 会いたいよ
“I want to see you right now.”
hold me tight
今夜も 一人 抱きしめるよ
Tonight, too, I hold it all alone.
永遠に 降る雪があるなら
If there was an eternally falling snow...
君へと 続く この思い 隠せるのかナ
Could it hide my feelings for you?
hold me tight こんな思いなら
Hold me tight - if this is how it feels,
誰かを 好きになる気持ち
I didn't want to know what it was like
知りたくなかったよ
to be in love with someone.
i love you 胸に 込み上げる
I love you - the feeling wells up in my chest,
冬空に 叫びたい
I want to shout to the wintery sky,
今すぐ 君に 会いたいよ
“I want to see you right now.”
hold me tight
i love you
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Bye-bye.